Now, let's do the effect of the hem of our jeans.
So I cut the fold-over side of the bottom,
and then deleted those sheets.
The effect of the hem,
we first make a more regular hem.
The regular hem,
we made it through a thin small strip.
We choose our bottom edge,
look at its length,
and then create a strip of the same length.
Then the height is very thin,
we are two millimeters.
Then we copy another pattern out,
copy a fabric out,
and apply it.
After applying it,
we sew it on the side of our pants.
Then the粒子間距和衝突厚度,
manually reduce it,
and then add it to the side.
We sew it,
and then add it to the side,
oxy.
Now we sew it again,
and then we sew it back.
Okay, then.
Give us this piece of fabric that new creation,
to apply a kind of毛发 ,
change its default hair style
to become our ROH denim.
This is the preset of a hem of our jeans.
Open our hem of the hem of the hem of our hem,
we can see a hem of hair,
and adjust the hair's rendering effect
we can adjust some parameters of the hair
to make it more suitable for the effect we want
For example, we can increase the thickness of the hair
and increase the thickness of the hair
and increase the density
For the color, we can add some texture
and add a light blue
About how to adjust the hair
We also have a master live class
You can take a look at the previous class
I didn't talk about it in detail
The method is to use a thin strip
and set the attribute of the hair
Then we control D out of the symmetrical panel
Then sew it
Because now our panel is not linked
So we have to sew it again
Okay, let's look at the rendering
The effect of the hair on both sides of the pants
is 1,5,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,18,19,20,21,21,22,23,24,25,26,27,28,29,30,32,32,33,33,34,35,36,36,37,39,40,40
We have rules here
We can save the file
Finally, what about the hairbing effect
Is a more subtle one
In this way we can see how to do it
Actually, the method is
It's also very simple
It's also through a board
Then apply our one
The effect of the sticker on the edge is made
This is our edge
One on the edge
Oh, it's not a sticker
A texture on the edge
So let's draw a board first
The width is the same as its width
The height is about five centimeters
The width is about seven centimeters
well
And then we sew it up
Use texture first
The adjustment of our texture can be adjusted after fixing the proportion in the attribute editor.
Then it can see a little bit of the edge in the 3D window.
We can bend its edge curve to green.
Then adjust its height.
You can't see it like this.
Then sew it on the edge of our hair.
Change the type of sewing line to Turned.
Select this version and add it to the outside.
Modify it.
Open our rendering to check.
Let's take a look at the effect.
You can see that the effect of our thinning edge is completed.